To silence stitch my ribs with smoke
Build altars out of every word I never spoke
My mercy was the womb that never healed
And I keep...
Once against the council of my bones
Watched you slip into the black
six what it's
back better than ever resurrected. After just a couple days of being the CULT of
Psyche, it's now the KULT of Psyche. A simple change from a C to a K might
seem rather innocuous, but if you look at the letter C, that's the third letter of
the alphabet, letter K is the 11th alphabet, what is 311? What is, it's
Calvin Klein, 311. What is 311? I don't know, you tell me.
11 11 11
KK oh
I don't know that didn't it was I don't it wasn't because of the work code
But I was thinking that maybe they I was like she's had a good idea to have it even if it's kind of like, you know
I'm in chic as like maybe that they think that's some kind of negative
But yeah, but I was thinking like lecture
I was like seriously getting so many feelings like the channel was gonna go down
I'm like and I can't believe it's stayed up this long like really hundreds of poor mom like seriously
so it's like maybe one was just like in like the
In like some like you know a file and you've got you know AI scammed it or something like that
I don't know it's just like they mean they just deleted all my content
Hundreds like or thousands of hours of work actually thousands of hours of work all gone
All I have left are like some of the shorts that I made you know
From some of the clips, maybe I have some of the some of the videos, but most of them I just said copy paste
So yeah, they're it's all gone. It's all gone. You know, but you know what it's called like destroy to rebuild
It's like a tower moment, but it's like is a tower gonna like destroy you or is the tower gonna
You know inspire you to rebuild and I already had stuff in the works guys check out
Nicole it's like a website like check out what's got what I've already like got so much there already
You can actually watch the show there if you want to watch the show there
I have it like a little movie theater there. It's kind of connected to twitch right now, but um, and then it will
It's playing the show live and stuff
And so if ever like, you know, I get kicked off a YouTube or whatever if I can build this website enough then
which I want to because it's gonna be a great website.
It's gonna have like a lot of inspiration,
a lot of information on it, a lot of cool stuff.
And just a way to stay in contact with me.
It's got the membership running through there now.
You know, I'm sorry,
I can't give you any like cool emojis for this chat,
but you know what?
Maybe I can do something in the Twitch chat
and that's the one connected to my website.
So we'll see, but let's have a look at the website
how it looks right now.
Let me pull something up.
Okay.
Like she's okay, so oh, okay, so hold up psyche. Okay, it's cold of psyche
Dot-com okay, and then oh my gosh, it looks really good. Okay, so look
Like look what I have so far already again. I
Wasn't just like just ball my life. I think I've been working on this for a long time
But it's like I had to like read tool a few times
Here's what it looks and I know I'm still gonna do like the kind of directory. I'm still working on that part
Okay, I can only do so much at a time, but so here we are it's called to psyche website there
Welcome to the cult of psyche a sanctum or wisdom where's a grin and revelation runs on Wi-Fi
This isn't just a website. It's living broadcasts have Oracle have algorithm where streamers become seers and creators by community in the current
Here consciousness is both the medium and the message
Okay, so I have like the initiate, you know membership available. There's a daily affirmation that will change
Let me see what do I got here at the doctrine but
Community has some sacred slogans know thyself or at least look fabulous trying the mission statement self-knowledge is the goal
But aesthetic is the path. Oh, I love that. Okay
Give more offerings coming soon
See teachings we have teaching the teachings are still on the through developed
So you can initiate, you can learn more about the cult,
blow it up, right?
And then Oracle, coming soon, okay.
Some stuff is still coming soon.
This is a Discord set up, right?
I wonder, Twitter, YouTube, I need to,
and I should call it X.
Okay, yeah, I'm still doing a little bit to do,
but there's gonna be the reviews.
It's not going to get okay, and then um, well, so good. Oh, I have a blog
Why join five transformative benefits and now it's the spot. Where's my theater? I have a theater here's two somewhere
You know, I have a theater
Media I think click on media
Watch live streams and look there I am I have all it all set up like right
So you can watch you can extremely to kick on to on to the website
Huh, and then there's gonna be I let me try to put another chat through this through this one, right?
Okay
But I can be on my website on my website. I can go I
Everyone
And it's gonna come on the screen a bit. Oh, I have to put after typing a whole thing. Hold on
Let's open this map, oh no, did I do, okay, well anyway.
I'm impressed, it looks good, huh?
I think it looks pretty good, okay, so anyway,
so there we are, and then I'm gonna have like,
I think I put a video up, let me see, oh yeah,
there's a lot, I do have another little video, still good.
If subject there's a gift or I don't know. There's good kicks. I don't know
I I mean that really this is like a kind of game. Have what I don't know quite how
We're gonna try it out we're gonna try it actually works pretty good for streaming though I
Just don't play any of these like I don't play only community. I have a few VR games actually
So how's everyone doing?
I know we had a little shock and it's like I think we're gonna get through it. Okay together
You like the terrible and it's cold stuff. Well, well electric. It's just like, you know what I think
It's more of the direction I like it is more my sense of
I know I like sexy wiggins tarot and stuff, but it's like and it's kind of like a tongue-in-cheek thing, too
And but it's also it's like all the stuff coming my mind together like at once. It's like, okay
This is just work. I just say it's just like stuck. I don't know. It's like right for some
I think it's beginning to bring into the world right and they even changing the CC to the K is like supposed to like you know
It's like something to why am I what's going on here? Oh
Something the mountain is like
Flickering green. Oh my god. I have I did like run a bath, but then it's like
I'm just so stressed, you know, and I would think probably got a little bit cold. So
No one else knows that it's okay. I want people to I want the people to like
And it is a cult I mean it's like there's like it's cool and it's not it's a culture
But it's like if you like look five minutes into it, you'll see, you know, I say it's like half completely serious and half
Completely a completely joke, you know, and that and it's like and you can choose people can choose for themselves
It's not a bad thing. I think it's kind of like a fun
Illuminati kind of parody
Because I do I am in the Illuminati, you know, so but anyway
We'll get to that story another day
okay anyway how are we doing oh my gosh I'm wearing these librarian glasses so
this is a Halloween happy Halloween guys it's actually what I'm calling it ghost
a wean this year because you know pork ghosts and putting through all this
stress and like you know he's trying to do it was great thing for me and you know
and it's I hope I think it's all gonna work out for everybody I love ghosts
thank you so much ghosts for even the thought you know even the thought of it
I appreciate you and I'm well, I'm still going if I if I have to eat ramen noodles and
you know and
You know a shop with cat food. I will I will I will survive. Okay. I won't shop with cat food. Oh, I I don't need to I don't really ever need to
Do that, but it's like, you know desperate times. It's like, you know
Well, I'll be okay. I'll be okay. It was nice having like a little bit of income, but it's like seriously. It's like I
Think I was making just as much or more with the cash app, and I think that's probably a better
System I get all I get all the donation rather than like a percentage of it
I get it all all
You know instantly instead of like once a month, and it's like and then it's not subject to like some stupid
Stuff which I really don't agree with you too big that much, but how they run it like oh, but it is
Whatever whatever. I'm not a partner anymore. So I guess I don't have to worry about also
I can like have a fun show like I wanted to I don't have to worry about I don't have such a
Hair across my asshole about everything because now it's like, you know what I already got my
website going with the kick stream on it so it's like what I'm what I feel like
I've actually upgraded you know I feel like YouTube is like it's like it puts
like a real constraint on your channel like not being able to like
Talk about certain things. There's certain things that you're not allowed
You're not supposed to talk about at all and I say and I can't even bring them up because if I do then take the strice down effect
Then I will bring attention to that and people will try to do it. So I don't I don't tell but I will tell you
Well, I came and tell you because then you'd be like you people would go attack channels
But I'll just say there's something there's one there's a certain country in a certain war
No, no, no, no, no, no, do not mention it
You're not eligible for monetization, and I know that's why so that's why I might have like ended a few shows kind of early and stuff, right?
There's no one's listening to me. I'm like, I'm like, let's not talk about global. I still don't want to talk about global politics
I don't know global politics stuff and like the domestic stuff is fine
Right, and I like going into like a little bit of like that conspiracy stuff
Which I'll be able to do more now because it's like I'm not like a monetized channel like really it's like
You know whether youtuber makes it or not it is a nice place to stream, right?
And it's like I'd like having you guys here very but the people that are here would probably follow me to the website
And like because you can actually get a notification when the show goes on and stuff. I bet
If you would you would say in touch with me like maybe bring people here and like maybe we'll have a better group and stuff
I mean, it's like I mean not I mean we're great
But it's like you know some of these people that were here
We're just like bringing the energy down so bad and it's they hopefully they don't find the show right but
You know
I guess I mean, maybe they will I mean, I just hope the right people find the show
I know I did a little ritual to like I like like like and it basically said like wouldn't matter what the news make everything work out for
The best for everybody, right? So
And then that was before I found out the news that the channel would not be
The appeal was not granted, right? The answered very quickly
and so
I'm not worried about ban evasion.
I'm not worried about fucking,
well, but I already had the last stream got removed
by YouTube because I was playing full songs on it.
And they're like, if you do that, okay.
Well, I was able to do that on my other channel
like all the time.
It's kind of, but there were very strict,
a little bit stricter, you know,
for people that aren't modest, I guess.
I don't know.
You know, and then I don't even like or want anybody to use the and we're with the heart of you are but you know what we're allowed to now
so
But don't say it like please don't say it like say ninja. Okay. Say ninja. Oh
I need to close
Okay, so what's going on you guys here I have a song for you
Going to song I know you do
I ever wanted was a spark not a throne all I ever needed was a light to call my own
The voice in the dark say, you belong here
All I ever wanted was truth and the static
A little bit of real and the world so dramatic
Kept my calm while the crowd threw stones
Built my
a MISS MATTER
from curse your name to bless your gift they laughed when I fell but I danced
in the dirt every scar I got just rewrote my worth all I ever wanted was to
free my fear to turn my pain into something
with hope in his chest. Either way, he's live on stream, and the shows just begun.
Like a seashell spell
Alexander's preaching with a tan
So divine sunscreen forgotten
He's turning to bright
With a rise to people already wrong
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
That is whispers the pot can't wait
Alexanderizes halo of foam
Welcome micro stations to your new home
We're the loudest people in the world
Snapping our claws at the call of the law
Before we raise it up
Snap in our claws at the cosmic law
It's like you Wiggins cult.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Oh my tummy.
Okay, yeah, they give me all these stupid Halloween frames
and now it's like, I can't post anything.
Hold on.
Delete, delete.
Now let me try it.
Oh, gosh.
I'm kind of exhausted a little bit.
Too much too much worrying. I don't need to worry. Oh my gosh. That's why they gave me all these dumb backgrounds. Hold on
I like a couple of them. I don't want to pumpkin with the
Pirate hat. I don't want that one ghost. Oh, there's the ghost. I'll keep the ghost
Ditas mortos. No
Trick or treat party that has bats on it. I like it. I like the purple. I like what is this one upside down what?
Upside down world
Okay, it looks better than the witches cauldron and we already had the ghost cauldron. So at least the witches cauldron bubbles dark
Okay, it goes cauldron cute spooky pattern. Okay
I mean I'm down for that. Okay, so let me see if I can now
post
that I
Can okay good
Now I can put this up on the top left. Okay, and look do you want to see what I like home?
You see some nice photos of me. I had some publicity publicity things drawn of me today
So see how you like it. I do like this one
Oh
How do you join you join like this you just click on the link like always you you sexy
Oh, I mean you look cool. You cool person
There you go. That's how you join buddy
Oh, join the dark side. You just go to my the cult of psyche.com and you can join the membership
For $20 you get you would get a
A 30-minute call every month at 30 minutes to discuss whatever you want with me. I think that would pretty much
Make all that worth it. So let me just I'm gonna
No, I have to look I'm gonna be a little more careful. I'm gonna put the banner on. Hello
Yeah
You guys that goes. How are you? Yeah?
Yeah, I'm gonna be back sir
Yeah, we're back already. Can you believe it? It wasn't even like a Harley. It felt like I left, you know, it was just like
I was on a panel of these neighbor talking shit
You know what they were talking about? They were talking about the ghost song. I was like, dude, that was a great fucking song
It was great. I can play it. I'm gonna play it soon. I mean, do I have permission to crash out to crush out already?
Did he say lecture never once read next step by the way, and she promised she would
you know i'm not going to be up to you and i you're gonna remix uh i'll play the ghost song here
do we have permission to crash out so let's see the ghost song where is it um downloads okay here
we go it felt lonely in these streets are we all alone had nowhere to go well now we're all now we're
Permission to crash out
Ghost already did it took the whole crowd
That goes through the night night
That's how you know the haunts a lot lights flicker
Chats in the right and somewhere goes
F***ing go!
F***
Heroes in loud like thunder
Run!
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghost just grins
Let's f***ing go!
Do I have permission?
Yes.
Yes!
I think he's there.
Yeah!
I'm finna cuss the fuck out yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
It's a dream
Beautiful
Let's go to Berseky, give me 30 seconds. I'll rejoin. Okay.
Thank you sir. Here's my new publicity photo guys. Here's my new publicity photo. Oh, I need to take
myself off here. Hey! What the fuck do you put me on the screen for? I'm trying to show
you the new publicity photo. Let me see if I can bring it up. Is it showing yet? No, it's not.
It's showing your fucking face. I can't see it
Well, no, well, it's my face
I'll do it later. Oh, actually, we'll save that one for tomorrow. Yeah
Okay, yeah, give me literally 30 seconds, I'll be right back. Okay
May I have permission to crash out you are ready now cost runs is down
Okay
So how do you like this one?
There we go
Where is everyone left? I mean you guys are such jerks
People that leave look I look so great. I
Like that a lot. I look wonderful. I have more to see what else I got
How about this one
I look so nice, but then I was like, I look too nice.
I was like, can you make me one where I like,
don't look like so nice?
And they did.
I'll show you what it looks like.
Oh, I don't know, maybe not.
Oh, it's asking for video files, all files, okay.
Did it put evil? So where's the evil psyche? I mean, there's evil psyche. I know I know I said make me a little bit darker
Or make it like look a little bit like more sinister
Because it looks like oh, it's like oh, I'm such a nice like, you know priest
Okay, I can get it. I'm gonna chat you home. Let me see library
Okay, yeah, I'll hear this. Okay, this is great
I do like the darker one, but I mean the lighter one. Oh, yeah, I guess it's in there, but I just didn't see it. Okay. Yeah, okay
So you see the light one, right?
It's the light. This is the light. Hold on. Here's the dark one
Having so much fun still let me see where's the dark right here look. Oh
It's the evil that I'm still I still that one up on
There oh
Ghosts is back on here's the evil one
Tell me how you like it
Ghosts look it's like the two psyches you see this one. Oh, there's this one see there's this one
Damn, you're ugly
I think I'm gorgeous
You said almost change it again. We'll change it to the other one. Yeah, yeah, that's not perfect
That's a little but you know that it kind of looks like Jesus a little bit, but I like this one the best
Very healthy, I don't know
Well, I mean, I can see the rhythm a little bit. It looks like you're long lost, you know
But he was you know, healthy or maybe why is there 28 messages? Oh, yes. Oh, that's a beautiful man right there
Oh, so think I need my glasses on yeah, it goes and so yeah, so I told you what
Yeah, the website's up man that man looks like a debater master debater
I may maybe a master maybe an apprentice
Maybe a pat, you know
What did they call like oh, yeah, they like when the two people masturbate each other they call it mutual masturbation
Maybe a mutual masturbate. That's called a circle jerk. You don't know what a circle jerk is
But if there's only two people then how can it be a circle it would be and it would still just be a line and then
Just because how two points doesn't mean the radius can't be a circle dude
Or it's not a circle it means over three people. Well, I mean here's your argument
How many people would it take to fucking make a circle?
Well, no, you can have as many as you want as long as it's more than three because it's only three then that's a triangle
Before it can be a four can be a square
Square between. Oh, so you make this hard you are day. It's a fucking circle
If you grab another man's wiener
Yeah
Would you like me to grab you don't don't start you don't start the game. Don't do it don't start it
channel
You said circle jerk first, you know what it is. Have you ever been anyone goes fuck you easy first of all second of all
You're making a dumb ass argument. I if we grab each other and so circle jerk. I mean, what are you making against that?
You could say three points three digs is a triangle four digs in the rectangle or square
You can make all day. It's a
Sort of right. I'm saying I'm doing great. You write Seccy's cult is dumb dumb
Hey, fuck you who's saying does
I did say dumb dumb. Well, I always say dumb. I'm a surprise
But easy, can you tell us like that he's wrong about the circle jerk? He doesn't know what he's talking about
He doesn't know anything about circle jerks ghosts. You're the only one who knows anything about them. So stop it before I make you
Oh, I know!
Oh, I don't know. Fuck, did you become a big divider, sir?
I've been a big divider, sir.
No, this is so you don't know the circle jerk is on summer's right now
What are you doing ghost
I'm not on summer right now. Don't fuck up. I'm talking to him not you know, I just literally was on there
I was talking to Athens and Alex. Are you Tony? Are they celebrating? Are they celebrating my demise?
I mean if you really want to make it a big deal screenshot what I actually said and send it to psyche
Cuz he's telling me to put the word out. You tell me I literally what I did say I did say dumb
Yeah, you know that screenshot it
I mean, that's that's your war cry. Why are you using your war cry about yeah?
Well, you told me to put the word out and you sure know I gotta put the word out the words not dumb dumb though
It's supposed to be like, you know
They were talking a lot of shit about you. They're saying that you're done
Okay, well they said a lot about the trip to you, but me now since we're getting along glittering off
Well, Athens for the first time ever
I mean
He's a bore he's a bore and I'll talk about whoever I want to it's my show again. Go ahead. Okay. Yeah, and uh
Yeah, fuck him and you know KZ actually like you know paid a few bucks to like you know start getting his
Privileges back, but hopefully people will just lose
No, I mean
Self monetize it with the with the cash app and stuff like that, but it's not it's a backup channel
It's like right now. This is just gonna be my YouTube presence from now on
I'm gonna have it monetize through power chat through his cash app
Making your main channel brother, but I have a backup. I mean it is it goes the other channel is just gone. It's
Yeah
All the content and everything I might I might be eligible and it's like it may be a year or half a year six months to
To restart it or something. They might forgive me because they just
I know but I but I'm I like this I like it
I like not monotony. It's like a little bit like less stress and it's like I can like fucking say what I want to say
I don't have to worry about people. Can I say that word?
Yeah, you can please do really can I
Yes, you can
All the rules are out of the window except like you know, just don't
I like it. Yeah, that's my voice. I have a humiliation fetish ghost and so I love it when you talk
I just wanted to like break to us. I don't feel like a badass my bad
Can you like put the word out though? If you go to my community while there's like a little like a picture
I said psyche or it says cult of psyche. It's cool with a K by the way cult of psyche calm
And I like this I like this I like to spin on it Nicole
I like it brother. You're doing a good job. Thank you. And the website was really perfect for it
And it's gonna have like so much cool stuff and it's like I already have like a lot of
The secrets on it and stuff. It's gonna it's gonna it's like got really things for you guys to like enjoy
I like how easy came over here
And he was only coming here to try to start drama because I didn't mention your name
I was like, so I can be fine obviously. I was thinking you know that brother
But I was like, uh, then I was like, yeah, his new channel name is cool. So I feel I spoke with a K
Dumb Dumb's I called them dumb dumb and he came over here and said that I
Trying to get me in sight. Are you like, all right?
He's trying to get us to fight easy. It didn't work. It didn't work
No, obviously it didn't work. If I wanted to debate him, I would debate and if I wanted to debate you, I'd debate you
He's just he's just looking to
Go for a little trouble. There's some people that want to watch the word burn, brother
Because they like, you know, everyone likes a nice campfire and stuff, but you know what I
Don't want to like, you know, it's like I like to like warm the house not burn it down and stuff
So let's like, you know, the last one was burned. I like I like to keep a moderate temperature
This I feel like it's revenge of the nerds because remember I'm revenge of the nerds like they had like, you know
The alpha betas like the cool thing or the alpha betas or whatever the cool kids like all attack them and like, you know
They take their house and stuff like that and then it's like then they then
They so the nerds just like fucking like
Get a new house and like and then it's and it's even better because they know how they know how to use like certain technology
And like their nerves, right? And so they can they make it like really cool
And then like the alphabet is like, you know, try to like, you know, trash it again. Like after they like
You know
The picture, you know, oh, I'm sorry. I'm gonna take it down. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry
I wish it happened to fucking join
We were actually getting along but you know me that's is I mean anytime I've ever talked to these people we've always argued
Don't it's just like he was just boring and then he was like and he said oh, that's why this channel is gonna fail
Whatever and it's like now. He's gonna say oh, I was right
No, I mean well, I would go ahead and break the argument like okay that one fell but guess what I mean didn't fail
It didn't fail it didn't fail it was it by you the whole thing
No, it didn't the the whole thing is it's like it's a whole it was probably it's probably been better because now
I have more freedom to like say what I want to say and not to worry
I have the whole but I have the whole like, you know website to support it too and it's like website
Theme together. It's all
It's all getting really cool. I mean, it's like I swear to you it's gonna be
Frickin even better than the YouTube monetization isn't great anyway, because it's like okay first of all
You know, it's like they take a huge percentage of it
And then it's like paid out once a month and it's like if you they even do pay you and it's like and then it's like
Damn your half. Oh damn your 50% I think
Yeah, so it's like it's like really like better just to like, you know use other other things and like, you know, it's like what's it called?
stream elements or whatever
power chat and
Cash app and that kind of cash
And I'll have other things on my website like don't make it easy to be easy to donate or check out
Anything I don't know. I have a lot of good stuff
Make to make things easier and more efficient and make it more like and I do love the cult idea because it's like it
Doesn't make it feel like more of a family. I don't know and not in a bad way
I think I've been getting caught a quote for years now and start with fucking Trump
And then it now is with uh, I can say the name word the fuck it I can say whatever I want now
Andrew Wilson
They call us in a call and like
They're doing both the definition call is that I that's why I'm glad you spelled it with a K
Yeah, well, and that's the german way. It's like, you know like uh, or you know, I think I think it sounds very
I think I well at least I know like, you know the word control
9 I'd ask a man is in it man his dog. She's a German Shepherd. No, we probably know
Yeah, so there. Oh, we're up. I can't you see. Oh, that's why
How are you? How are you? Oh my gosh, my hair is not very good
Yeah, so
You already know
Oh God, he was talking shit about it's on summers right now
What I said his new channel name is caught in cycling dumb dumb slug
Well, I'm not enjoying the I thought he could be just talking to the shit no live right now
Yeah, I'm gonna turn it show I'm just trying to show love for the new channel brother, but I am also looking for
You know, you know, I could get down there. Well
Debating so much man. It's giving me gray hair. My hair's falling out
Yes
Well, I'm still just actually playing on earth, right? I am gray
You're wet don't say don't do not say anything weird
You were thinking that
I love you brother. We're Jamie. Does Jamie want to come up?
Jamie Jamie would you like to come up you're being summoned to the stage? Yeah, she always talks shit to me
She might as well come up and just hang out. We'll actually get along
Very rude person by the way
Are you rude are you rude Jamie? I don't think she's rude. Yeah, she's being rude to ghosts. Yes. Yes being rude to ghosts
Oh gosh, how dare you?
Her knife. Oh, oh god
This the second page don't fuck I told you his new channel is
Cult of psyche you keep up in psyche terrible readings
Easy would you like to come up here? Let easy on here cuz I gotta explain shit to him
Like I gotta use really small fucking words and it's hard
Easy like how can I say?
How can I say like it's kind of weird though, like I can say war but I have to say fight with him
Like he doesn't understand like yeah, obviously you have to fight in the world like it's hard to talk to this guy
In all these New York people, I'm calling everybody out from New York all of them
Anybody from New York wants it?
Once you're done done get
And that's on
That the war cry dum dum
Yeah, you're a main case
Some ass we know dumb ass. We're on this page. You know that can I crack? Don't I'm right and ask that
Yes, you may crash out. I don't want permission to crash out. So I crash out. I don't know
No, it's not gonna be bad. We're actually we're not monetized. I think the fuck I want just you can
Oh
Yeah, hey easy come up tell you New York what he's come up. Let's come up Alice come up. I'm ready to come up
I'm crashing on everybody. I'm super the fuck I want to date weird
Finally I got permission
You may have permission to crash out
Well, I wouldn't I would have joined but you're still sitting here watching done for Mars will come up
Now we're getting some people over here. Let's go
Yes
Got people Johnny's a dumbass easy to retard he also
Also, he he fucks around like he claims he's not gay, but I mean he's like both know that you know
He talks around but also if you want to join on down Jamie if you want to sit there and type in the chat
That's cool, but if you want to join let's run one anybody that wants it. I'm calling all New York people as well
Anybody that wants to run come up here. I'm not monetizing so I can not monetize
I can say the fuck I want let's run one. Let's see how it really goes tonight
The DC's the whole purpose of the song and all I don't have to ask the mission
Yeah
We're not we're not playing guys
We absolutely
Are here to shit happens all these people and by the way clip and shit the Athens
Well, not somewhere. Oh, they're going the Athens Alex. Oh, there's like a TPM race
How the shit about a psyche come on come shit, but no, let's run
Well, no one's gonna talk it. Well, I mean, they're you came in
Well, I'm up here and running. I guarantee they're not gonna run. I guarantee but I'll be awesome to fuck down
Some people already came in try to rub it in my face, but it's fine because you know what?
So I will on this ghost here. Nope
Nope, exactly goes to here now come back up. Let's run it
Come on up guys. I wasn't big. All right big boys here
Don't think anybody's in the chat. I think nobody knows about the show anymore. So it's like all right
I mean they kind of do but I don't think I think I think at this point. It's yelling
Yeah
I'm doing my yeah, I don't have to I can see the fuck I want right
Yep, you can
No, I'm just gonna say it. I'm not dude. I don't break to us. You know, that's a habit I got into like German take-out
You know how bad take-out is nowadays?
Yeah, it's terrible you can you say sir, I
Can say it simp I said it
Ban them ban them open the ship at worst
You know what you should listen to the song I have on a I'm taking this I want to dedicate something to you
You don't mind bro. I'm dedicating this shot to you. Okay?
Shot you had a long day at work. I'm taking a shot and I'm gonna dedicate to you, bro
Now tell me you love me. I love you. Okay, I'm taking the shot you
Wow
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Oh
What do you just don't do not start you not do it
They couldn't don't me not start what do you mean? What do you stop the game? I'm not being gay. I
Am being really yeah, not being gay. I just
You can be small listen here's Martin. You can be straight
But if you have a sister
Unless you're from Alabama, that's gonna happen. You can be gay if I'm your brother. So don't stop to gage it
Okay
Be respectful, yeah, because if we were to gay together that'd be against us because we're like brothers, right?
Well, we'd be in Alabama or Western genius or and I am from Western
perfect
You live near the you live near like that like what do they call the out of Appalachia's?
Appalachians
Yeah
Well, don't crash out here, I don't have any beds available. I'm just kidding. It's Bates motel. It's all
All they can see
So
So did you know like I'm trying to see let's see
I'm not literally have to copy the link of your new channel because any
Panoramic they're like, oh you're like this way. What happens like I'm just gonna have to like
Okay, put your tongue back in your mouth first. Thank you sir. Play the what?
That's it put your tongue back in your mouth. Yeah
Okay, so I'm gonna I'm gonna read you the initiation ritual so that the annual or other emergency meaning of the fraternity in Grand Conclave
Assembles at the great Bacillens shall be seated in the corner of the platform occupying his desk
All ex-grand base EL should be seated immediately behind the grand base EL so all on his right shall be seated the grand keeper of records
Know uncle's boring though. It's like a lot of paperwork. Hold on the grand marshal shall occupy a seat near the grand
Vitalis I think that's me or best Alice. What does this mean? I don't know. Oh, hold on. Where's the initiation part? Okay, okay?
This is just instructions. Oh my gosh
It's so so many words. I'm not gonna steal this one from Michael. I'm gonna use I'm gonna make my own
I'm gonna just do this one's too complicated
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Okay, well, this is getting ridiculous.
Do I have permission to crash out?
Ghosts already did he took the hole down
Okay, well guys, can you like share the share this live and like let people know that I'm like still around and like I'm like fine
Thank you for sharing the
My show on summer's ghosts. I appreciate you
Okay, guys, it's a little bit of an emotional day, but you know what?
I feel like I just took a huge dump and I feel so much better, right? So hopefully
Hey, Joanie, what's up girl?
Hopefully we're okay. Oh Joanie, are you spamming the chat? I need I need to yell at nightbot
Yeah
Yeah, okay
Well ghost has been distracted by some other show, so okay here. I
Love you guys. Oh my gosh. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, the main page is gone, but you know what I?
Remain
Let me see oh
Think thank you so much. I don't know if you want me to mention, but thank you so much. Oh, you're so sweet
Thank you so much
Oh, I appreciate you
It's a little gonna be a little bit I think that ultimately
It's gonna like improve the atmosphere of the room
Okay, I don't think some people like we're gonna like kind of like lose them and they're not gonna know where I went and then
There is not going to come back at whatever or like I think maybe some scared away some people like with the cult word or whatever
That's good, too
I like people that want they get to the joke about it at least like or let know me well enough to know
the culture and some of the thing so
Johnny, here's a song from today. I posted this right before my channel went down
But it's just so appropriate for today. Here's the song
I'm sorry, take two.
And because nobody tell me some more, I am.
I remain.
I'll be with you.
I keep reopening it just to
Against the council of my bones watch you slip into the black where the current
And I agree with that, Joni, like, um, I, uh, I just got these like very strong psychic messages that it's like everything is as it should be.
It's like a clearing.
It's like, and I love starting over.
I do love fresh starts.
I love just taking out the trash and like, like some of the, some of the people, I mean, it was just like terrible, right?
And it's like, so they have most force, the darkest before dawn, but you know what, things are, things will work out.
think that I was on a negative trajectory or it's like it was I was down
down to crash and burn with that one but you know what it's called learning to
fly like right and learn to fly sometimes we have like a little like you
know even if it starts out like a great flight there's turbulence and like no
you know we're learning to fly like a little baby bird you know just coming
out of the nest and I felt fell on the ground right and
Some cat licked me up, right? But
The cat just played with me a little bit and just like left me
Under the tree to die and I was able to climb up and eventually they're gonna fly again. I don't know. It's a terrible analogy. I'm so sorry
But look I have you guys here
This is like the quality I've been looking for.
It's like the quality of people rather than the quantity.
I don't care if there's a hundred people in the chat
of like nobody is like, you know,
you know, like contributing the conversation or the vibe.
I mean, it's like, if there's so many people here
just to like look at a, like a, you know,
have people like slow down, look at a car accident.
That's what it is.
My show is sometimes like, not like it's an accident,
but it's like, it's just like some,
it's like a spectacle.
Sometimes you just like,
Want to look and you don't you don't really like care about you know
Me or the channel it's like the people like you're just like wanting to see like some kind of like terrible thing happen
It's a it's kind of regrettable. I'm gonna be changing the
The tone though, so I'm gonna do I'm gonna do our horoscopes tonight you guys cuz and and I'm at a tipping point. Yes
There's no more left on the road. Yeah
Joni, go to cultofpsychee.com, K-U-L-T, of Psyche.
And see how much like work I've done on it.
And it's like, it's coming together so cool.
It's gonna be so cool.
I'm just just starting on it.
And I believe, of course I believe you.
I believe it.
I believe everybody here can like do amazing things,
you know, manifest their dreams.
The tower yep, exactly it was a tower and sometimes and I was like I got the tower before like recently and I kind of
I was like, oh the tower and that but I said something during that particular tower. I was like
There's towers that
Will destroy you and there's towers that
Clear out energy right
Yes, yes, and so I will bring up these
I had this little slideshow designed.
See, I think this is it.
Yes, okay, we have areas.
Okay, so let me get out my notes.
And we can go over our fun Halloween horoscope.
Okay, we can go areas, shoot.
Hold on, this one's calling me.
Oh, hold on, I need to go on mute.
Yeah, I don't think so
Do they want to they want to are they calling me over
Okay
No
Well, I'm hopefully somewhere with it anyway, but yeah, somewhere is like a good friend
Okay, okay sounds good
Yeah, yeah, I'll get the word. Thank you
Okay, I'll watch for you. Okay. Thank you
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK
No change of plans
I'll come on
I'll come on a little bit later, and I'll do the horoscopes. I'm gonna go do a little publicity
Which is important to do when I'm restoring my channel
We can go over to talk your ish. I think that's summer's channel. We'll see what happens over there. I mean I
answer some questions and
We'll go sit on summer's channel. We'll see how it goes. Okay. Love you guys. I'll be back probably today